<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TJ Crew Captains on</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in TJ Crew Captains on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Core Workouts</title><link>/core/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/core/</guid><description>Feng Core This is a core workout created by one of TJ Crew&amp;rsquo;s greats: John Feng. Legend has it that John Feng would do three sets of Feng Core without taking a break or breaking a sweat. This is a 10 minute core workout that works your stability and will make your shoulders sore along with your abs. The workout is as follows:
90&amp;quot; plank 60&amp;quot; side plank (left) 60&amp;quot; side plank (right) 60&amp;quot; plank 60&amp;quot; plank to pushup 60&amp;quot; swing/side to sides 90&amp;quot; Knee to elbow (basically mountain climbers) 60&amp;quot; leg and opposite arm extended 90&amp;quot; plank Post pic to Swole Call</description></item><item><title>Offseason Rowing</title><link>/offseason/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/offseason/</guid><description>Resilient Rowing Summer Racing Program For Those Serious About Rowing and Live Closer to the Occoquan than Washington, D.C. Dates: June 6 - July 30, 2022
Location: Sandy Run Regional Park (where TJ rows)
Resilient Rowing is a program that many TJ rowers have joined since they row out of the Occoquan. Coach Jon has coached for them and will coach for them this summer. Note that they have bids for the Head of the Charles Regatta 2022 (world&amp;rsquo;s largest regatta) in the Men&amp;rsquo;s Youth 4x+ and Men&amp;rsquo;s Youth 2x events this fall.</description></item><item><title>Summer Competition</title><link>/competition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/competition/</guid><description>We are holding a summer workout competition! Here is how it works: you do a workout (can be anything), use our conversions to calculate how many points you scored, and then log them in the Google Sheet. Whomever scores the most points by the start of school wins!</description></item><item><title>Training Plans</title><link>/plans/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/plans/</guid><description>It is extremely easy to lose all of the gains you made during the season. Try to do something during the summer and you&amp;rsquo;ll reap what you sowed in winter training and on the water in the spring. An easy to stay in shape while also being &amp;ldquo;lazy&amp;rdquo; is to just do steady state while watching movies. Jonathan got through a lot of the Marvel Cinematic Universe last summer (2021) while doing 3x20:00/5:00r.</description></item></channel></rss>